[Music] Hey
[Música]
guys, it looks good, it
buenas que tal chavales se ve bien se
sounds good. Well, I'm not going to be here
escucha bien bueno voy a estar poco
long because we've been arguing, it went
tiempo porque nos hemos alega ha
on too long with the previous live.
alargado mucho con el directo anterior
I think we're going to be in less time and finally he
creo que vamos a tardar menos y al fin
showed some seriousness. Here we are
ha mostrado una barbaridad ya estamos
back from vacation. Okay,
aquí de vuelta de vacaciones vale a
starting tomorrow, let's go crazy. Let's go
partir de mañana pues caña que te cagas
crazy both on the
caña que te cagas ya tanto en el canal
main channel and the secondary channel, as if the CEO were
principal como el secundario como
interested in all of them. Okay, I wanted to not
interés al ceo en todos vale quería no
miss this live broadcast
dejar pasar este directo
to tell you about this because it seems
para comentaros esto porque me parece
totally incredible to me since on this
totalmente increíble ya que en este
channel in particular there was a debate with
canal precisamente se hizo un debate con
this character, a debate in which he was
este personaje un debate en el que quedó
totally exposed and humiliated. Well,
totalmente expuesto y humillado bueno
we did two debates with him, okay, in
hicimos dos debates con él vale en los
both of them he was totally exposed and
dos quedó totalmente expuesto y
humiliated, but the last one um was about
humillado pero el último um fue sobre
Tom Jones, not exactly the one in which he
tom jones 'precisamente no en el que
ended up asking for forgiveness. Javier, thank you very much, I mean,
acabó pidiendo perdón javier muchísimas
the guy is supposed to have
gracias o sea el pavo se supone que
ended up asking for forgiveness.
acabó pidiendo perdón
I was freaking out when you
me he quedado flipando cuando me habéis
told me this news. I'm going to watch it, I'm
comentado esta noticia voy a ir viendo
going to watch it
la voy a ir viendo la
because we're freaking out, I'm going to start watching the
porque vamos alucinando voy a empezar a
video, the tour, okay, I'm going to start
ver el vídeo el tour vale me empezará a
watching the video, the surfing and all these
ver el vídeo el surf y todas estas
little things that  you guys passed it does
cosillas que me habéis pasado
n't
no
exist
existe
what's reacting to tommy's video
que está reaccionando al vídeo de tommy
and his disgusting morality four months
y su asquerosa moralidad cuatro meses
later the same video
después no se sigue el mismo vídeo
is still like this
es así
today there are no stipes or eyes today I'm
hoy tampoco hay estípites o los ojos hoy
not sorry
tampoco lo siento
another dry [ __ ] like this
otra [__] seca como este
on twitter churra but I delete it but what about so what is what
en twitter churra pero lo borro pero que
could someone tell me that
lo de tan que es lo que me podría decir
what about town I'm being
alguien que lo de town me lo estoy
told by several people in the chain I
diciendo varias personas en el chain no
have no idea what about what it is me
tengo ni idea de lo que de lo que es yo
but the referee
pero el réferi
luckily a single death of the kid
por suerte una sola muerte del chaval
thank goodness it would be like very sad more
menos mal sería como muy triste más
has left the networks
ha dejado las redes
ah okay this was I
ah vale esto fue
understand that this has been when the
entiendo que esto ha sido cuando el
kid got worse not before the death
chaval empeoró no antes de la muerte
and well guilty
y bueno culpable
obviously because yes
obviamente porque sí
[Music]
[Música]
the hate
el hate
if you want to see the comments I'm going to
si queréis ver los comentarios los voy a
make a video here don't throw people at
hacer un vídeo aquí no tiréis gente a
anyone okay I mean you can give your
nadie vale o sea puede dar vuestra
opinion without any kind of problem I believe
opinión sin ningún tipo de problema creo
in freedom of expression and I think we
en la libertad de expresión y creo que
are all in favor of it but to
todos estamos a favor de ella pero para
give your palate your point of view and to
dar tu paladar tu punto de vista y para
document something that
documentar algo que
[ __ ] that is worth it you don't need
[__] que valga la pena no te hace falta
any insults to anyone okay to anyone to
ningún insulto a nadie vale a nadie a
anyone  Okay, you
nadie vale
can just have a
puedes super sencillamente tener un
really strong argument without insulting
argumento super fuerte sin insultar a
anyone and come across as a real
nadie y quedar como un verdadero
gladiator, okay, but without insulting,
gladiador vale pero sin insultar
driving with music,
manejando con música
this kid is not right,
este chaval no está bien
and well, basically what I wanted to
y bueno básicamente lo que quería
comment on,
comentar
the first video was
el primer vídeo
surpassed without anything, without understanding a damn thing,
superado sin nada sin entender un [__]
excitement with the [ __ ] that is, it also doesn't
de emoción con los [__] que es
need much context, the clip does
tampoco necesita mucho contexto el clip
n't need excessive context, the
de tampoco necesita excesivo contexto el
clip
clip
deserves a glass of wine, that's what
se lo merece un vino berza es lo que
happened before, each one in the end has
pasó antes de cada uno al final tiene
its followers,
sus seguidores
I
yo
made a video that was almost a cover, I
le hice un vídeo que era casi un cover
made a video that we could have
le hice un vídeo que podríamos haberlo
considered it and not seen and then on top of that we
considerado y no ver y luego encima
had two debates in which it was
tuvimos dos debates en los que quedó
game over, but I don't know how this kid
game over pero yo no sé cómo este chaval
has people who watch him doing these
tiene gente que lo ve haciendo estas
stupid things
burradas
[Music]
[Música]
Four months of 2011,
cuatro meses de 2011
in four months, the 2011 channel has reached
en cuatro meses el canal 2011 ha llegado
the peak of eight million four hundred
a la cima de ocho millones cuatrocientos
[Music]
[Música]
Two months ago, I think a video is okay, okay,
hace dos meses creo que un vídeo vale
and finally has views, okay, okay,
y por fin tiene visitas vale vale vale
okay, here's the law, I wanted to get to this
vale aquí está la ley esto quería llegar
because I know the views, okay, Tommy, where he
porque se las visitas vale tommy donde
had a total of one million domains of
tenía un total de un millón dominios de
views, I can swear that the videos
visitas os puedo jurar que los vídeos
that have  uploaded here to androids did not
que ha subido aquí a androides no
reach 200,000 and what happens it did not
llevaba a las 200.000 y que pasa no
reach 200,000 and what happens to give to
llegaba a 200.000 y que pasan a dar a
the visits that it has or stops having on
las visitas que tenga o deja de tener en
Tommy's channel if the question is not the
canal de tommy si la cuestión no son las
visits to the subscribers that it has or
visitas a los suscriptores que tenga ni
anything for the century the question is the
nada por el siglo la cuestión es el
detail
detalle
is the cause and the create in him kid
es el causar y el crear en él chavalillo
well the dream that he wanted to what he was
pues el sueño que quería a lo que él
looking for and what in some way
buscaba y lo que de alguna manera la
people have wanted to give him as a good
gente ha querido brindarle como un buen
gesture which is
gesto cuál es
showing that they are subtle people do not
demostrando que son sutiles la gente no
see their videos understand what the
ve a sus vídeos entender lo que la
second part of this series of videos
segunda parte de esta serie de vídeos la
people suffered to comb
gente sufrió por peinar
I am from rengo city next to quinta de
soy de rengo ciudad contigua a quinta de
tilcoco where this is from to me the whole
tilcoco de donde esto me toda la
community is shocked as for
comunidad está conmocionada como para
someone to do something as miserable as those of you have them
que alguien haga algo tan miserable como
that they threw you no no it
los de se los tienes que te echaban no
is fine be how the [ __ ] could it be
no está fino sea como [__] podría ser
these gods the kid wanted to do it I would be
estos dioses el chaval quería hacerlo
11 years old I think he was no the
tendría 11 años creo que tenía no el
kid did not have a dream before dying
chaval no tenía un sueño antes de morir
which was to be on youtube and the whole community
que era ser youtube y toda la comunidad
has come together to fulfill the dream eight
se ha unido para cumplir el sueño ocho
and a half million  subscribers the
millones y medio de suscriptores el
kid
chaval
has been happy fulfilling his dream that
ha sido feliz cumpliendo su sueño que
then has had visits he had no visits
luego ha tenido visitas no tenía visitas
that have subscribed to be subscribed
que se han suscrito por ser suscritos
to make him fulfill his dreams jealousy
por hacerle cumplir sus sueños celos
is that it was the purpose literally I
es que era el propósito literalmente se
leave the networks and they attacked his mother we
los dejo las redes y atacaron a su madre
will open average to see what happened
abriremos average a ver que lo que pasó
programs that this one has does not have to
programas que éste tiene no tiene que
be on the internet really is that I already
estar en internet de verdad es que yo ya
since what happened four months ago
desde lo que pasó hace cuatro meses
the apologies he made were because he
sale las disculpas que hizo fue porque
felt cornered here in the live
se sintió acorralado aquí en el directo
no
no
literally the apologies were because he
literalmente las disculpas fueron porque
felt cornered in the live
se sintió acorralado en el directo
when I looked at it
cuando lo mire
holy god
dios santo
the kid's visit does not matter he was not going to
no importa la visita del chaval no iba a
live off youtube or earn a salary I don't
vivir de youtube ni cobra un sueldo ni
even think the channel would go up
siquiera creo que el canal subiera
monetized I don't know if the channel would ever monetize I do
monetizado no sé si llego a monetizar el
n't think people requested it
canal no creo que lo solicitaran la
to understand that the kid has
gente a entender que el niño
not spent a month without being a member
no me he pegado un mes sin ser miembro
because I did not have the euro milestone in the account
porque no tenía el eur hito en la cuenta
so as this month I have finally gotten a
así que como este mes he conseguido un
job I give you this so you can
trabajo por fin te doy esto para que lo
enjoy it churri this is missing about
disfrutes churri está hace falta sobre
this kid I saw the video playing the
este chaval vi el vídeo haciéndose la
victim today mediocre and does not  lack
víctima de hoy mediocre y no hace falta
of truth you did it in a hurry you want it do
de verdad lo hicisteis apurado lo desean
n't make a superhuman effort to
no hagáis esfuerzo sobrehumano para
donate okay but still thank you very much
donar vale pero igualmente muchísimas
whoever can become a member is
gracias el que puede hacerse miembro
desired and whoever can't not
deseada y el que no no
online at any time has given has
en línea en ningún momento ha dado ha
given pain to people has given pity and has
dado pain a la gente le ha dado pena e
never used pity as a weapon
nunca ha usado la pena como un arma la
people because it still seems incredible to me the
gente porque aún me parece increíble los
[ __ ] you had like this [ __ ] [ __ ] do
retrasados tenías como este subnormal de
not understand what I am
los [__] no entiendan que me estoy
telling people even if I say it
diciendo a la gente aunque lo diga
is the people problem face and the people
es la gente problema cara y la gente
problem because I wanted to be a good act
problema porque quería ser un acto bueno
it can be a statement.
puede ser un comunicado.en
man you do not subscribe to the channel of take out of
tío tú no te suscribes al canal de tome
pity
por pena
or at least not in my case
o por lo menos no en mi caso
subscribing out of pity is not that you
suscribir por pena no es eso te
subscribe because you yourself feel
suscribes porque tú mismo te hace
excited to participate in fulfilling the dream
ilusión participar en cumplir el sueño
of the kid that he had before leaving his
del chaval que tenía antes de irse a su
channel I do not remember what account but
canal no me recuerdo con qué cuenta pero
I subscribed it
me suscribí
is true words man because I knew what he
es verdad palabras tío porque sabía lo
was looking for with it
que se estaba buscando con ello
each one has his life and each one has
cada uno tiene su vida y cada uno tiene
the circumstances that he has okay and that
pues las circunstancias que tiene vale y
is what there is some
es lo que hay
things happened to
a algunos les tocó las cosas a otras
others but it is simply and simply for
otras pero es simple y sencillamente por
the detail of contributing so much to this
el detalle de contribuir tanto a este
kid
chaval
and on twitter people have finally gotten
y en twitter por fin la gente se ha
tired of the subject the word
cansado del tema ya es que la palabra
subscribe out of pity is a bit like I
suscribirte por pena es un poco como yo
would believe that more empathy is appropriate I would
creería que corresponde más empatía lo
call it empathy I don't know normal I don't know
llamaría empatía no se norme no sé
exactly why the words but to take it
exactamente por qué las palabras sino la
out and strict markets and there are times
sacar y mercados estrictos y hay veces
that we interpret them as we
que las interpretamos como las
interpret them and so on to me the word
interpretamos y demás a mí la palabra
out of pity is a bit strong
por pena me resulta un poco fuerte
I do it a bit more to say wow
yo lo hago un poco más por decir [__]
look at this kid this thing happened to him
mira este chico le ha pasado esta cosa
it's empathy the word you
es empatía la palabra tú bien lo has
said it well the south let's see here the
dicho el sur a ver aquí empieza lo
strong part starts no but look at the faces and without
fuerte no pero mira las caras y lo sin
listening to what he says look at the faces he
escuchar lo que dice mirar las caras que
's putting his foot while those things
está poniendo el pie mientras esas cosas
I know we're talking about an
yo sé estamos hablando de un chaval de
11 year old kid who has died and who was expected to
11 años que han muerto y que se esperaba
die
que iba a morir
from childhood cancer dude for
por un cáncer infantil tío desde hace
four months and we knew everything he was going to
cuatro meses y lo sabíamos todo iba a
die and you've spent the last four months playing
morir y llevas los cuatro meses tocando
the dick cellos I
la [__] chelos
mean can he really sleep at
o sea de verdad puede dormir por la
night can he sleep at night
noche se los puede dormir por la noche
thinking that a kid has appeared in
pensando que ha aparecido un chaval en
the community
la comunidad
who had a dream before dying of being a
que tenía un sueño antes de morir de ser
youtuber and people have turned to so
youtuber y la gente nos hemos volcado
that the kid  reach millions of
para que el chaval llegase a millones de
subscribers that there was no intention
suscriptores que no había una intención
for the kid to live off youtube,
de que el chaval viviera de youtube
be a child prodigy, be a huge success,
fuera un niño prodigio fuera un exitazo
not simply for him to live his dream, for
no simplemente que él viviera su sueño
him to be happy, for him to
que él para él fuera feliz que él
live a dream that today they are subscribing to me,
viviera un sueño de que hoy se me están
the time he has left and you have been
el tiempo que le quedará y tú has estado
the time he had left touching your
el tiempo que le quedaba tocando la
dick, you are a piece of [ __ ] of people, the
[__] se los eres una [__] de personas
other one I say it so clearly
el otro lo digo así de claro
as a person I no longer care what you do
como persona ya me da igual lo que hagas
as a youtuber that you have dedicated yourself although
como youtuber que te has dedicado aunque
to content of [ __ ]
a un contenido de [__] [__] ya lo
we have already commented here in its day we did not
hemos comentado aquí en su día no te
make you like a species and you do not see your
hicimos como una especie y no ves tu
content [ __ ] I mean you were dedicated
contenido [__] [__] o sea te dedicabas
to charging for thanks that looks at me
a cobrar por gracias que a mí me mira
Paulo nothing Paulina or Karim is a problem
paulo nada paulina o karim ea problema
is dedicated to creating content of
está dedicada a crear contenido de [__]
[ __ ] that was dedicated to putting your face
[__] que se dedicaba a poner tu cara
in a corner while putting
en una esquina mientras que ponía vídeo
original videos okay and you have been as
originales vale y tú has estado ya como
no longer as a content creator what you have
ya no como creador de contenido lo que
done no the condal has been the roll is
has hecho no el condal ha sido el rollo
useless as a person but this affects
no sirve como persona pero esto afecta
what you are as a person does
lo que eres como persona tiene en la
that guy have in his head making fun of a
cabeza ese tipo hacer mofa de un niño
newborn child  deceased recently deceased and
recién fallecido recién fallecido y que
not recently deceased that we knew
no recién fallecido que sabíamos por
unfortunately that sooner or later this was going to
desgracia que tarde o temprano esto iba
happen unfortunately yes I swear that it
a pasar por desgracia si os lo juro que
hurts me a lot from here to send
me duele muchísimo desde aquí mandarle a
the best of my love and my support to
los mejores de mi cariño y de mi apoyo a
that family okay I go I am a father I
esa familia vale voy yo soy padre
have two children and I can not even
yo tengo dos niños y no me puedo ni
imagine the pain they have to be
imaginar el dolor que tienen que estar
going through now and that they must have gone through
pasando ahora y que han debido pasar
all the months to have
durante todos los meses para tener a
this guy this is what the internet has you
este tío esto es lo que tiene internet
know that's why I always try to instill in
sabe por eso yo siempre intento inculcar
people that the other day I saw a
a la gente que el otro día vi a un
youtuber who said no I do not understand the
youtuber que decía no no entiendo la
nonsense of protecting minors well
tontería de proteger a los menores pues
look at one of the examples of characters
mira uno de los ejemplos de personaje
that you can find you can
que te puedes encontrar te puedes
find characters of many types it's been a
encontrar personajes de muchos tipos es
long time that they do very
de mucho tiempo que hacen cosas muy
bad things but one of the types of jealousy that has
malas pero uno de los tipos de celos que
led us since it was publicly known
nos lleva desde que se sabe públicamente
that the child had the cancer that he had being a pain in the
que el niño tenía el cáncer que tenía
ass trying to boycott the
dando por culo intentando boicotear el
child's dream trying to make fun
sueño del niño intentando cachondearse
of that humor
haciendo humor de eso humor
how can you sleep alone at night you have
como puedes dormir solo por la noche has
been the four months of the limit of
estado los cuatro meses del límite de
fulfilling his dream while the child was
cumplir su sueño mientras el niño se
dying touching your balls man
moría tocando los [__] tío faltando
disrespecting the family man
el respeto a la familia tío
already as a person it is a  hatch
ya como personal es una escotilla
dead
muerto
now I can say that Tommy's channel
ahora puedo decir que el canal de tommy
is dead right now it's
está muerto verdad
not going to upload anything
ya no va a subir nada
so the people who say it's still
así que la gente que dice que todavía es
better are praising a dead man
mejor están están alabando a un muerto
a dead channel
a un canal muerto
now I can put in their empathy in
ahora puedo poner en su empatía en
necrophilia
necrofilia
what a miserable guy I would have many
qué miserable tío tendría muchos
adjectives to put on you and that are going through my
adjetivos que ponerte y que se me pasan
head right now but I'm not going to say it
por la cabeza ahora mismo pero no lo voy
wow god what disgusting people you've
guau dios que asco de personas
been bothering me for the four
has estado dando por culo los cuatro
months while the child finishes
meses durante el niño mientras termina
dying you're already making fun of the fact that
moría ya te cachondea de que se ha
a child with cancer has died you have a child
muerto un niño con cáncer tiene un niño
who did not deserve to die
que no merecía morir
well you still make dark humor with a
pues todavía hace humor negro con una
person who deserved to die not with a
persona que merecía morir no con un
criminal of serious acts no who have
delincuente de hechos graves no que han
done very bad things in life and
hecho cosas muy malas en la vida y que
in the end they have sought their death they
al final se ha buscado su muerte lo
wish that they have murdered people I don't know
desean que haya asesinado a gente no sé
yet but the fact is that he is a child
todavía pero es que es un niño una
innocent creatures who did not deserve what
inocentes criaturas que no merecía lo
happened to him man they will go enjoy
que le ha pasado tío irán a disfrutar de
life and you laugh and you laugh at you have
la vida y te ríes y te cachón de has
or audio and on top of that with these faces and this
o audio y encima con estas caras y esta
beautiful
hermosa
wow god there are people who should be
guau dios hay gente que debería estar
condemned to live under a bridge I can think of  so
condenada a vivir bajo un puente a mí se
many
me ocurren muchos adjetivos
derogatory adjectives that I'm not going to put for
descalificativos que no voy a poner por
8 on youtube okay but it seems to me that I
8 en youtube vale pero me me parece es
couldn't sleep at night it's that on
que no podría dormir por la noche es que
top of that you are like this you are this type of
encima que eres así eres este tipo de
person
persona
[Music] you
[Música]
do it on the internet are
lo haces en internet
n't you ashamed dude I'm
no te da vergüenza tío
going to put in chat mode the member mode
voy a poner en modo chat el modo miembro
that he asked me to
que me ha pedido que lo pongamos dos
put it two members and he's going to give up yes no or audio wow and we just saw a click that we are going to find just seeing his face makes me angry and on top of that the guy played the victim I don't know how he has such a big face playing the victim cancer in his head is an idiot
el cáncer en la cabeza es imbécil
the child said the mother
el niño dijo la madre
in the comments the mother would see it
en los comentarios lo vería la madre
when they had blocked do you know what
cuando tenían bloqueados sabéis acaso lo
happened
que ha pasado
look at your uncle the family is destroyed there will be the
fíjate tu tío la familia deshecha va el
day that he gets on the internet in
día que se meta en internet dentro de
ten years
diez años
or five years to remember how
o cinco años para recordar cómo se volcó
people turned to the internet and is found
la gente con el internet y se encuentra
in the videos of this [ __ ]
en los vídeos de este [__]
imagine being the father of the kid
imaginaros ser el padre del chaval
and wanting to remember this with affection
y querer recordar esto con cariño
and in contrast the characters apologies
y en contraste los personajes disculpas
to you because with  none of
con vosotros porque con ninguno de
you [ __ ] people
vosotros de [__]
think you're
creéis que sois
5 and 30 for you with me in nipples I
5 y 30 para vosotros conmigo en pezones
didn't throw you out we are made fatal gowns I'm
no te echaba nos esté hecha batas
sorry but how many videos has he made have
lo siento pero cuántos vídeos ha hecho
started making a lot of
se han puesto a hacer un montón de
videos now he
vídeos ahora
has started to be a lot of videos
se ha puesto a ser un montón de vídeos
about everything and about him being dead you
sobre todo y sobre que está muerto
only want
sólo queréis
my mother this kid
madre mía este chaval
of my aunt
de mi tía
is that I don't even know what comment
es que no sé ni qué comentario
was cured his song
se curó su canto
is hurting people a lot
está haciendo daño a personas a muchas
this click was before the m of the child
es clic fue antes de la m del niño
also depending on reich
también dependiendo a reich
you see putting a lot of people in controversies
veis metiendo a mucha gente en polémicas
of people attacking me who never gets
de gente atacándome a mí que no se mete
into controversies
nunca en polémicas
wow it doesn't surprise me because I know it we already
wow no me sorprende porque sé lo ya
know that a repugnant person
sabemos que una persona repugnante la
we have had here on the channel I mean
hemos tenido aquí en el canal o sea
we have two debates with him
tenemos dos debates con él
this character
este personaje
without any collaboration with this
sin ninguna colaboración con este
character already 62 debates in his day
personaje ya 62 debate en su día
you can go see it in fact I
podéis iros a verlo de hecho me di
realized that something was happening because suddenly
cuenta que algo pasaba porque de repente
many visits were coming to those
estaban entrando muchas visitas a esos
debates and why doesn't he cancel this guy well
debates y por qué no cancela a este tipo
look I can't open it now because it does
pues mirad no puedo abrirlo ahora porque
n't break me of course okay but precisely precisely
no me parte claro vale pero precisamente
that it doesn't break me  klaus let's see if I have
que no me parte klaus a ver
put it on youtube
le he puesto a youtube
or
o
many kids defended this person
muchos chicos defendieron a esta persona
saying that it is humor then saying that
diciendo que es humor luego diciendo que
he was only warning and in his last video
él solo advertía y él en su último vídeo
on the channel he says that we are
del canal dice que nosotros somos
insensitive pffff I can't now if
insensibles pffff no puedo ahora si
last bits I
últimos bits
don't know what's wrong with his head I
no sé lo que tiene la cabeza yo tuve ha
had a tweet saying we
puesto un tweet diciendo lamentamos
deeply regret the departure of tome 11 we
profundamente la partida de tome 11
send our condolences to his
enviamos nuestras condolencias a su
family friends and followers in this
familia amigos y seguidores en este
difficult time
momento tan difícil
a very big little one who managed to
un pequeño muy grande que logró
unlock our hearts and
desbloquear nuestros corazones y
achieve his biggest dream alongside
alcanzar su más grande sueño al lado de
all of us thank you tome and
todos nosotros gracias tome y le he
I have put it very well now close on the
puesto yo muy bien ahora cierre en el
channel to this guy who is making fun
canal a este tipo que se está burlando
of what happened to him
de lo que le ha pasado
zero tolerance this is not humor no and
tolerancia cero esto no es humor no y
nothing I had he responded to me
nada yo tuve me ha respondido
saying hello javi
diciéndome hola javi
potestades another account also we
potestades otra cuenta además
understand what he tells us if you think
entendemos lo que nos comenta si crees
that the video is in compliance with the rules
que el vídeo en cumplir las normas
report it
reporta
support it
la apoyan
support it with youtube
la apoya con youtube
I saw his 4 hour live and it made him
me vi su directo de 4 horas y le dio una
angry even more people leaked things and
rabia es más la gente filtró cosas y
when he acted like the victim it was
cuando se puso como la víctima fue
when some close ones walked away
cuando algunos cercanos se alejaron
not the 4 hour live now no  I'm going to see it I'm
no el directo de 4 ahora no lo voy a ver
going to see the clicks exactly
voy a ver los clic exactamente
but loves incredible youtube closes the
pero ama increíble youtube cierra el
[ __ ] channel twitch has closed the channel
[__] canal twitch le ha cerrado el canal
no no they have not closed
no no se han cerrado
man it
tío
's simple
es simple
when someone does something I'm going to screw it
cuando alguien haga algo voy a [__] lo
anyone who attacks offers the same line I'm
cualquiera que ataque ofrece misma línea
going to enter a secondary account I'm going to
voy a entrar una cuenta secundaria voy a
take all the information and I'm going to
[__] todas la información y voy a
publish everywhere
publicar por todas partes entre de sobre
especially the
todo
funniest in fact what he just
los más graciosos de hecho que acaba de
said is that apparently they have
decir es que por lo visto se lo han
wished it on him and they are publishing their information there
deseado y están publicando por ahí su
and look at what he had said
y mira en lo que había dicho
precisely that you don't have to
precisamente eso tampoco tenéis que
do it because in the end you commit it
hacerlo porque al final cometéis usted
is a crime but look at what he was
es un delito pero fijaros lo que estaba
saying something I'm going to screw it
diciendo el algo voy a [__] lo
anyone who attacks offers the same line
cualquiera que ataque ofrece misma línea
buoyant some secondary accounts I'm going to
boyante unas cuentas secundarias voy a
take all their information and I'm going to
[__] toda su información y voy a
publish everywhere that's where it
publicar por todas partes entre de eso
all comes from then he also still can't
viene todo luego también sigue sin
find any real information they have
encontrar información de verdad a pote
done it to him said colleague
le han hecho dijo colega
in this problem but in
en este problema pero real en la vida
real life it's very simple I'm not going to send
real es muy simple yo no voy a mandar a
you to insult this type of things
que te insulten este tipo de las cosas
that there are any day they will go without Lopez
que haya cualquier día le van sin lópez
thank you very much this guy any
muchísimas gracias este tío cualquier
day they are going to do something to him long
día le van a hacer algo
live the moderators of  it's
que vivan los moderadores de it
incredible youtube closes the [ __ ] channel and
increíble youtube cierra el [__] canal y
urges people to pass the clip
os insta a la gente pasando clip
close the [ __ ] channel shot
cerrarle el [__] canal tiro
you know what you have to do
sabéis que tenéis que hacer ustedes
answer my tweet
contestar a mi tweet
loud and mine from youtube for what he
alto y mío de youtube por lo que me
responds to me answer him with all these
responde contestarle con todos estos
clips telling them that they have no
clips diciéndoles que no tienen
shame youtube what the [ __ ] are you doing I'm
vergüenza youtube qué [__] hacen
going to
yo voy a
make you lose everything subscribe to
hace que pierdas todo suscribirte a
accounts send gifts
cuentas mandar regalos
enter sites that you have to enter that's how you
entrar en sitios que tienes que entrar
screw someone up in front I'm
así es como se jode alguien a frente soy
such a screwed up
tan [__]
mother of mine of a character [ __ ]
madre mía de personaje [__]
with a lot of power is to piss me off how much
con mucho poder es cabrearme lo mucho
the many bore me and we continue
los muchos aburrirme y seguimos
and if you get me to open you have screwed me
y si consigues que abra me la habéis
the crash
el choque
this wants please what the [ __ ] is this
esto quiere por favor qué [__] esta
sauce at night there is a lot of desire they
salsa por las noches hay muchas ganas
closed the channel and another channel was already opened
le cerraron el canal y ya se abrió otro
in tweets he makes fun of people
canal en tweets se burla de las personas
and believes in his little head that he is a victim he didn't
y cree en su cabecita que es una víctima
even apologize sorry but
ni siquiera se disculpó perdón pero
rocks deserved
rocks merecido
well he created another channel you say they
pues ha creado otro canal tú dices los
close them thanks to miriam thank you very much
cierran gracias a miriam muchas gracias
if they have created another channel tweet it will
si se han creado otro canal tweet se lo
close it quickly tomorrow good
cierra rápidamente mañana buenas
love dominant of love I don't have much
amor dominante de amor no tengo mucho
more to say
más que decir
funny
gracioso
about this you can look for grace
de esto se puede buscar la gracia en
this is him
esto es él
that I found out by how
que yo me enteraba por cómo se abre por
reason opens again and it pisses me off that even
otra vez la razón y me cabrea que hasta
at the end they gave me the reason you
en el final me hayan dado la razón ti
until the [ __ ] end until the final point until
hasta en el punto [__] final hasta en
the final point of this story they
el punto final de esta historia me han
gave me the [ __ ] reason
dado la [__] razón
or rather something that quietly playing and
o sea algo que tranquilamente jugando y
suddenly this doesn't make sense
de repente esto no tiene sentido
I thought
he pensado
my dick
mi [__]
Carlo about me okay and they just
carlo de mí vale y me acaban de
confirmed to me that the child has died this
confirmar que ha muerto el niño
is possibly the
está posiblemente la vez
saddest time that the song will have
más triste que va a tener la canción
sincerely it
sinceramente
is one of the times in which I
sea una de las veces en las cuales me
regret being right on this subject
arrepiento de tener razón en este tema
in the subject I mean
en el tema ósea
what a [ __ ] disgusting society what disgusting
qué [__] asco de sociedad qué asco de
people from Marbella
gente de marbella
I was before he
fui antes
has a ponytail now that we can
tiene una coleta ahora que podemos
count how long his attacks last once he
contar cuánto duran sus ataques una vez
has died on Saturday once they have
que ha muerto el sábado una vez que no
nothing let's see
tienen nada vamos a ver
how long they last okay how long are they like this
cuánto duran vale cuánto están así
attacking what they think is the bad guy
atacando a lo que creen que es el malo
which is me
que soy yo
not so that they give me even more reason
no para que me den aún más la razón
my mother it's
madre mía
not that this type of
no es que este tipo de
news is sad the child has died I did
noticia es triste el niño ha muerto
n't know this beginning well this controversy started
no sabía este inicio pues empezó esta
and it doesn't mean anything more
y no quiere decir nada más
d
d
wow
guau
we made
hicimos
8 minutes I'm not going to watch it what
8 minutos no lo voy a ver qué es lo que
that's what blocking the comment the band people on your channel you don't care children and with that three that solve things and then you know I sent those screenshots I have set everything to private I don't know if it's going to work but well go telling me what you don't see in public obviously the
que no veáis en público obviamente las
reactions are not going to be uploaded for the moment
reacciones no se van a subir de momento
because the guy
porque el tipo
reported for harassment this is the same as
reportar por acoso esto es lo mismo que
when he did to me no the turkey
cuando hizo conmigo no el pavo lo
criticized him the winter thank you very much put
critique el winter muchas gracias puso
a tweet criticizing him for what the
un tweet criticándolo por lo que por la
other time he was messing with
otra vez que se estaba metiendo con
Tommy making fun of his illness
tommy burlándose de que de su enfermedad
and the guy sent his people to report me
y el tío mandó a su gente a reportarme
for harassment you pissed off
por acoso tocaste los huevos
that he is a person of you
que es persona de ti
if someone knows who has leaked my
si alguien sabe quién ha filtrado mi
private information it
información privada
makes me very angry a child has left to
me da mucha rabia se ha ido un niño al
whom he has caused a lot of that wave of
que él le ha propiciado mucho esa ola de
negativity and the only thing he cares about is
negatividad y lo único que le importa es
proving that he was right on a stupid point
probar que tenía razón en un punto
but that he was right
pero que tenía razón
outdated where he says that I live on
desactualizada donde dice que vivo en
this street
esta calle
pass me what the report is not going to be long in coming
pasen me lo que la denuncia no se va a
and according to leather influence
hacer esperar y según influencia leather
of tweets believe me that the direct is going to be
de tweets créeme que lo directo va a ser
[ __ ] compared to me I understand
una [__] comparado conmigo lo entiendo
oh what threats are you making not in such a way
ay qué amenazas estas no de tal manera
not if the information is outdated why are you
no de si está desactualizada la
going to sue
información para qué vas a demandar
calm down how are you going to report someone who has
tranquilo cómo vas a denunciar a alguien
posted information of yours that is
que haya puesto una información tuya que
no longer yours and then there's the jealousy thing that
ya no es tuya y luego está lo de celos
was trending if you saw it it was
que fue tendencia si lo viste fue
trending yesterday yesterday what happened is that you
tendencia ayer ayer lo que pasó es que
asked me a lot yesterday when we were
me pedías mucho ayer cuando estábamos
with the Nobel Prize and all that you asked me
con lo del premio nobel y demás me pedís
a lot to talk about the subject but I didn't want to
mucho que hablase del tema pero no quise
talk about the subject because it seemed to me like taking
hablar del tema porque me parecía como
advantage of the vitality of the
aprovechar la vitalidad de la muerte del
child's death to make videos so I
niño para sacar vídeos entonces yo me
wait tomorrow and this guy has
espero mañana y este tío si se ha
taken advantage a lot we don't see what he has
aprovechado bastante no vemos que ha
released well
sacado
all these videos 10 videos 10 videos
pues todos estos vídeos 10 vídeos 10
in 4 hours
vídeos en 4 horas
10 videos in 4 hours
10 vídeos en 4 horas
to earn I
para ganar
was working editing videos for
estaba trabajando editando vídeos para
people and now I'm working with a
la peña y ahora estoy trabajando con una
bad mood on top of it that's crazy I don't know how
mala [__] encima que flipas no sé cómo
beings can exist on this platform
pueden existir seres en esta plataforma
really a greeting javi less than 3
de verdad un saludo javi menor que 3
thanks god of the bed get a lot of sleep
gracias dios de la cama ten mucho sueño
literally 10 videos in a [ __ ] hour
literal 10 vídeos en una [__] hora
is the new undertaker
es el nuevo enterrador
10 videos in a [ __ ] hour in 4 hours of
10 vídeos en una [__] hora en 4 horas de
walk thank you very much but
camino muchas gracias pero es que
literally
literal
the first one in an hour is five in the
la primera en una hora son cinco en la
last hour is five
última hora son cinco
how embarrassing it was to take you
qué vergüenza dio para llevarte que
how much you want and 20 euros my goodness my goodness
cuántas ganas y 20 euros
well he uploaded a video but I do
madre mía bueno ha subido un vídeo pero
n't know if I'm going to be able to put it because I don't
no sé si lo voy a poder poner porque no
like the keyboard to restart the computer
me va el teclado de reiniciar ordenador
so I can go
para que me vaya
but he uploaded a video it's that I'm not going
pero ha subido un vídeo es que no lo voy
to be able to put it
a poder poner
and jealousy
y celos
and he pasted it in the search engine to upload a
y lo pegó en el buscador a subir un
video saying that this is the end let's
vídeo diciendo que este el final vamos a
see you see it my goodness what scum
ver que lo veáis madre mía qué escoria
man
tío
I suppose that this maybe is the channel so
supongo que este quizá sea el canal así
on his side the last video of the
que por su lado el último vídeo del
channel
canal
maybe tomorrow all channels
quizá mañana todo canal
but they have put some strikes on
pero que han puesto algunas strike en
youtube they have also
youtube también
put it I fall asleep live and we
la han puesto me duermo en directo y
do a
hacemos un
sleeping it's 4
sleeping es 4
don't go go
no os vaya
everyone against me
todo el mundo en mi contra
so everyone touches you your
así que todo el mundo te toca te los
balls
huevos
reactions we
reacciones
passed at once but here it has
ya pasamos de una vez pero aquí
happened at the highest level
a pasada en el máximo nivel
haha nobody beats juanjo's 30
jaja a nadie le gana a los 30 de juanjo
man we are talking about in 4 hours 10
hombre estamos hablando de en 4 horas 10
in 4 hours 10 video of the death of the
en 4 horas 10 vídeo de la muerte del
child that you are making fun of
niño del que te estás cachondeando
because he is dead I do
porque está muerto
not have much to  to do is the truth
no tengo mucho que hacer es la verdad
of the channel
del canal
is what I do the most this video for
es lo que más hago este vídeo para
the few people who wonder what
la poca gente que se pregunte qué ha
happened
pasado
or leave a mark
o dejar huella
[Music]
[Música]
I'm pretty bad I'm not going to lie to the
estoy bastante mal no voy a mentir al
poor thing
pobrecito
poor thing is bad but there have
pobrecito está mal pero
been quite a few people who have
ha habido bastante gente que me ha
literally left me
dejado literalmente
sep
sep
some more problems than others but
unos más problemas que otros pero
during people who sent me to hell
durante gente que me mandó a la [__]
because if they haven't
porque si no
seen anything for the group
se han visto nada por el grupo
take it off
quita
but no
pero no
dinners must cry
cenas debe llorar
so
así que
[Music]
[Música]
to many people
a mucha gente
a big greeting without weight Daniel gained
un gran saludo sin peso daniel ganó
subscribers and then the lost ones
suscriptores y luego los perdidos a
the song is personified Mariano to
la canción está personado mariano a
someone gave him the money
alguien le daba el dinero
mother atheist that is not to
madre ateo que no sea
think that
pensar qué
between kindness and a-7 to think that people would
entre la bondad y a-7 pensar que gente
betray me like this it is incredible
me traicionaría así es increíble
traditional presents it
presenta tradicional
is incredible
es increíble está reventado
this fatal charlatan is busted
este charlatán fatal
according to the reason this subject is of the
según la razón de este sujeto es de la
pity that we felt for Tommy and that
lástima que sentíamos por tommy y que
we are hypocrites and for giving him the
somos unos hipócritas y por darle los
saps that he can not have and now
saps que él no puede tener y ahora
being at the top the why are they going to
quedando en la cima el porque le van a
be by winning by the mouth in front of an idiot
ser al ganar por la boca delante idiota
people
la gente
do not count anything also half crying
no cuenta nada también medio llorando
nothing more for nine minutes
nada más durante nueve minutos
but pretending not  pity
pero pretender al no pena
will stop you the sorrows freaking out I hope he
te detendrán las penas flipando espero
gained
que ganó
followers he
seguidores
gained followers while he was
ganó seguidores mientras que se estaba
making fun of the line had gotten worse and
burlando de la línea había empeorado y
then he lost them now in the end that he
luego los ha perdido ahora al final que
will have lost other followers I have not
habrá perdido otros seguidores no lo he
come but he gained followers I
han venido pero ganó seguidores yo
to the Chinese and that youtube could not
a lo chino y que youtube no se pudo
win to see tweets to close the channel
ganar a ver tweets a cerrar el canal
okay he says that another one has been created it doesn't matter they are
vale dice que se ha creado otro da igual
going to close it you can't create
se lo van a cerrar no se puede crear
another channel
otro canal
on youtube yet if you can dodge it
en youtube todavía si lo puedes esquivar
okay youtube they close your channel and if you
vale youtube te cierran el canal y si te
open it others don't realize you know if you
abre otros no se dan cuenta sabes si lo
do it with others they don't realize but on
haces con otras no se dan cuenta pero en
twitter not in tweets if they give you close the
twitter no en tweets si te dan cerrar el
channel in tweets the moment you
canal en tweets en el momento que te
find it they will come back to you and it won't take
encuentres te lo vuelven a chapa y no
long to find you because he doesn't stop
van a tardar encontrarte porque no para
screwing up and such no well nothing kids I do
de cagarla y tal no pues nada chavales
n't know what they think seeing themselves crazy pine
que no sé qué opinará verse loco pino
deleted things that cross my mind
borradas que se me pasan por la cabeza
but I'm not going to say it because it would be
pero no lo voy a decir porque sería
absurd basically
absurdo básicamente
I think the same success with those
yo creo que el mismo éxito con esas
words I think dallas is going to be a
palabras creo que dallas va a serle un
video in fact I'm going to try to see if I
vídeo de hecho voy a intentar ver si
can get into dallas' channel but
puedo meterme en el canal de dallas pero
like  I don't have a keyboard right now
como no tengo teclado ahora mismo
let's see if you're subscribers I'll enter
a ver si sois suscritos me meto
subscriptions and I
suscripciones y ya no
'm no longer subscribed through the main channel it
estoy suscrito por el canal principal
must seem to me around here Dallas
debe parecerme por aquí el dallas
needs them urgent psychological help
se los necesita ayuda psicológica
totally hey but the trot
totalmente oye pero el trote
because I'm here in the thumbnail of
porque estoy aquí en la miniatura del
outbreak 6 live now and he didn't
brote 6 directo ahora y él no
now said
ahora dicho
look man the buffet
mira tío el buffet
the last day take it
el último día tome
could be Dallas glass
puede ser vidrio de dallas
at the same time
a la vez
pig the
cerdá la
a uploaded the video now a couple of hours
a subió el vídeo ahora un par de horas
then I would have to be around
entonces tendría que estar por aquí
here the video doesn't appear here nothing I
no me sale aquí el vídeo nada
loved
amaba
everyone making the video of
todo el mundo haciendo el vídeo de se lo
my gay asks for it no truth is today's topic
pide mi gay no verdad es el tema de hoy
but listen to myself I said to myself the Dallas video doesn't appear it's that
pero escucha me dije no me sale el vídeo
the video doesn't appear to me really I
es que no me sale el vídeo verdad la
wanted to see it because they told me it
quería verlo porque me han dicho que
says something well it does
dice algo
n't appear I can't do anything else
pues no me sale no puedo hacer otra cosa
and here
y aquí
and then here
y luego aquí
thanks in gel
gracias en gel
blind habitat where the hell
hábitat ciego dónde [__]
here the [ __ ] is the video he left us
aquí [__] está el vídeo se nos fue para
forever
siempre
take 11 so he doesn't remember he's a
tome 11 para que no se acuerde es un
child but he was a child who had a
niño pero era un niño que tenía una
very aggressive disease they feared for his
enfermedad muy agresiva se temía por su
life and that finally here at the beginning it
vida y que finalmente aquí al principio
was up to here the beginning
era hasta aquí el principio
is the and forward in his day I did  a
es el y adelante en su día yo hice un
video supporting him loses the people who
vídeo apoyando le pierde la gente que
subscribe to his channel because his dream was to
suscribe a su canal porque su sueño era
be a youtuber the good thing is that he
ser youtuber lo bueno es que lo
achieved it okay the good thing is that while he
consiguió vale lo bueno es que mientras
was alive we gave him hope throughout the
estuvo vivo le dimos ilusión de toda la
story that council there are people who
historia ese concilio hay gente que se
subscribed for the people who supported him
suscribió para la gente que lo apoyó
we have something to focus on something to
tenemos algo en lo que centrarse algo en
make videos about and although we couldn't
lo que hacer vídeos y aunque no podíamos
do much from our position
hacer mucho desde nuestra posición
because we weren't his friends or his
porque no éramos ni sus amigos ni sus
parents or anything it showed something good and that is that
padres ni nada demostró algo bueno y es
many people many millions of
que mucha gente muchos millones de
people could join together to give him something
personas se podían unir para darle algo
a child with such a big problem says
un niño con un problema tan grande dice
hope while he was alive
ilusión mientras estaba vivo veíamos
many of us saw hope that he
muchos de nosotros de ilusión de que él
was going to get ahead he was going to overcome
fuera a salir adelante iba a superar
this but in the end it couldn't be like that I
esto pero finalmente no pudo ser así
was following him in the last few days while he
estuve siguiéndole en los últimos días
was hanging he's been
que andaba colgando lleva ya par de
uploading videos for a couple of months now he activates the
meses en subir vídeos activa el teclado
on-screen keyboard it doesn't matter I
en pantalla da igual ya me volví a
restarted the computer again to put the title
reiniciar ordenador para poner el título
to the excerpt and he looked clearly
al extracto y se le veía una clara
worse in time nothing he couldn't
desmejoría en tiempo nada no ha podido
overcome it this has already been confirmed by the
superarlo ya está confirmado esto por la
family and anyway I wish them the best
familia y en fin les deseo lo mejor
since that sad video not only to
desde aquel triste vídeo no sólo para
say this and honestly I had
decir esto y honestamente había pensado
previously thought about not making this video
anteriormente no hacer este vídeo
mainly because there are many issues
principalmente porque hay muchos temas
of those who do not speak because I feel that I am
de los que no a hablar porque siento que
not going to contribute anything and that I simply
no voy a aportar nada y que simplemente
suffered something the same as another person
padecía algo igual que otra persona
can say the cold simply not
puede decir el frío sencillamente no
speak and also it would bother me a lot
hablar y además me molestaría muchísimo
and honestly it bothers me personally
y honestamente me molesta personalmente
the people who both in the previous day
la gente que tanto en el día anterior
and will probably happen in this
como probablemente va a pasar en esto
also say that I am
también se dicen es decir que yo ando
trying to get attention when
intentando llamar la atención cuando
literally my previous video was to
literal mi vídeo anterior era para
support him defend him the people who
apoyarle a defenderle la gente que le
were criticizing him that at another level of
estaba criticando que a otro nivel de
this era I will
esta era
make a video pesify mind speaking
haré un vídeo pesificar mente hablando
option of disgustingness it was
opciã de asquerosidad de verdad era
absolutely in embarrassment or low asked
absolutamente en bochorno o baja pidió a
him he is going to get it they are the
él se lo va a pillar son la de
disgusting envious people who are dedicated to
envidiosos asquerosos que se dedican a
going out there to say [ __ ] arrest
salir por ahí a decir [__] arrestar
envious of a child who had that
envidiosos de un niño que tenía ese
problem and who had gotten many
problema y que había conseguido muchos
subscribers disgusting and pitiful it disgusted me a
suscriptores asqueroso y penoso me dio
lot and despite the fact that my video was
mucho asco ya pesar que mi vídeo era
to support tell people to
para apoyar a decir a la gente que
subscribe to his channel and support him and
suscribir a su canal y apoyarle y
defend them there were people capable of saying
defenderles hubo gente capaz de decir
that I was trying to get
que me estaba intentando llamar la
attention from that when I am I can
atención de eso cuando esté al puedo
make a video about anything else if I
hacer un vídeo de cualquier otra cosa si
did it is because I really felt it  and I
lo hice es porque realmente lo sentí y
felt the rage that it gave me there were people
sentí la rabia que me daba hubiera gente
criticizing him, envious, ridiculous people
criticando le envidiosos ridículos
dedicating themselves to saying stupid things about him and it
dedicándose a decir burradas sobre él y
also makes me very angry and today they
también me da mucha rabia y hoy en día
also do after the child
también lo hayan después de que el niño
who is not with us there are people
que no esté con nosotros haya gente
capable of doing garbage making fun of him
capaz de hacer basuras burlándose de él
when he is not even here look look at the
cuando ni siquiera está mira mire el
boy thank you very much here it is disgusting
chico muchas gracias aquí es asqueroso
now we will talk about it but seriously it
ahora hablaremos de ello pero en serio
made me very angry at that moment and I
me daba muchísima rabia en ese momento y
was about to make a video
estuve a esto de hacer un vídeo
responding to all the
respondiendo a todos los comentarios
garbage comments but I did not feel like continuing to
basura pero no me apetecía seguir
deal with the subject on my channel because I
tratando más el tema en mi canal porque
honestly preferred to leave it because I had already
prefería honestamente dejarlo porque ya
done the good deed that I could
había hecho la buena acción que podía
do that people said to subscribe
hacer que decía la gente que suscribiera
and for the rest with a lot of
y para resto con un montón de métodos
different methods these types of problems
diferentes este tipo de problemas de
again you do not have to be a doctor you do not have to be
nuevo no tienes por qué ser médico no
that chemical you do not have to be
tienes por qué ese químico no tienes por
the end well nothing we will react
qué ser el fin pues nada reaccionaremos
to the video when I upload we will react to
al vídeo cuando suba reaccionaremos al
video 2 upload
vídeo 2 suba
guys I'm going to bed thank you very much
chavales me voy a la cama muchísimas
to all of you who have
gracias a todos los que nos habéis
accompanied us throughout the night both
acompañado durante toda la noche tanto
in this one and in the previous live
en este como en el directo anterior que
we had a great time with dallas and
lo hemos pasado muy bien con dallas y
With Acumar,
con acumar
subscribe to Kuma's channel, of
suscribiros al canal de kuma por
course, to Dallas's, I won't tell you anything
supuesto al de dallas no os digo nada
because I'm sure you're in the mornings. Okay,
porque seguro que lo estáis las mañanas
see you tomorrow
vale mañana nos vemos
this week. Once I leave, I'll leave tomorrow.
esta semana una vez me voy me voy mañana
See you later. A kiss.
nos vemos un besito